ALEJANDRO LÓPEZ BESTEIRO

09021982

(+34) 637223576 alelopbes@gmail.com www.lopezbesteiro.es

PROFILE

A multidisciplinary designer, with adaptable skills to meet the requirements of any project, whether editorial, corporate, web or mobile services. As a front-end developer, my experience includes both small-scale and large-scale projects a professional adapting to any work situation.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Designer / front-end developer at Basebone

June 2013- Present

In a first stage, my work covered the design of campaigns, web pages and the creation of graphic material for the marketing department. Currently, my work focuses on the design / development of internal tools and the corporate image of the company.

Graphic designer/front-end developer at Yoin

January 2012 - December 2012 (12 months)

Yoin aimed to be a micropayment application through mobile platforms, fully developed using web language. I was part of the design group, helping to create the graphic and development material and the one in charge of the front-end.

Graphic and web designer at i2Factory (Huelva)

February 2011 - August 2011 (7 months)

My work, as a freelance, for this technology company involved the creation of graphic and interactive projects. Taking part in projects such as the creation of a mobile application for the Latin American Film Festival of Huelva.

Advertising department (as an intern) at Onda Local de Andalucía (O.L.A) (Sevilla)

July 2010 - September 2010 (3 months)

Internship in OLA (Onda Local de Andalucía) in the advertising department performing tasks concerning the design and development of campaigns.

Graphic designer and layout designer at Revista Sogel (Sevilla)

June 2010 - July 2010 (2 months)

I was in charge of the design and layout of the first issue of the women's magazine "Sogel". In my internship I carried on with the task assigned previously by that magazine and finished the entire publishing project.

Graphic designer and layout designer (as an intern) at Revista Sogel (Sevilla)

February 2010 - April 2010 (3 months)

Internship as a designer and layout designer for the magazine "Sogel", free magazine focused on women.

Photographer (as a intern) at EL Mundo (Huelva)

July 2009 - August 2009 (2 months)

Internship as a press photographer for El Mundo Huelva Noticias (a local newspaper).

Photographer at Agenda Cultural Live (Sevilla)

February 2008 - April 2008 (3 months)

Co-worker photographer at this entertainment guide.

Cameraman (as an intern) at Antena Huelva (Huelva)

April 2006 - June 2006 (3 months)

I carried out some of the practical work period of my degree at this local TV station, developing camera skills.

Lighting technician (as an intern) at Proinso (Huelva)

May 2005 - June de 2005 (1 month)

Internship for the Lighting technician course. The internship took place in the entertainment company "Proinso" as part of the team in charge of lighting.

EDUCATION

"Licenciatura en Publicidad y Relaciones Públicas" **(five-year degree in Advertising and Public relations)** by Universidad de Sevilla

September 2006 - June 2011

Certified technician in Image /Ciclo Formativo de Grado Superior **(A higher education course)** by Instituto Pablo Neruda (Huelva)

September 2004 - June 2006

Assistant technician in Graphic design, Curso FPO **(a course of professional training)** organized by FAECA (Seville) with a duration of 630 hours 2008

Lighting technician / Curso FPO **(a course of professional training)** organized by Proinso (Huelva) with a duration of 850 hours 2005

Programmer in digital photographic report and image scanning /Curso FPO **(a course of professional training)** organized by Ánfora Formación (Huelva) with a duration of 235 hours 2005

SKILLS

- Upper Intermediate level of spoken and written English.
- Upper level of spoken and written Technical English
- Driving licence holder.
- Teamwork skills and ability to perform as team leader.